It's Magic, Charlie Brown is a family, animation,
comedy film directed by Phil Roman.
When Snoopy turns Charlie Brown invisible in a magic
act, he has trouble changing him back.
Charlie Brown (Voice), played by Michael Mandy.
Peppermint Patty (Voice), played by Brent Hauer.
Sally Brown (Voice), played by Cindi Reilly.
Linus van Pelt (Voice), played by Rocky Reilly.
Lucy van Pelt (Voice), played by Sydney Penny.
Schroeder / Kid / Franklin (voice), played by Christopher Donahue.
It's Magic, Charlie Brown is the 21st prime-time animated television
special based upon the comic strip Peanuts, by Charles M.
It originally aired on April 28, 1981.
The film explores themes of american football, magic show,
boy and dog, invisible person, alchemy.
The tone is lighthearted.